# Nhlakanipho Mlangeni

2352 Block 5 0614448336/ 0623573030

Soweto Nhlakaniphomlangeni1@gmail.com

Thulani

Information Technology in Technical Support and Cybersecurity Pentest+ I acquired my qualifications at Richfield Institutional College, Digital Youth ICT academy and Afrika Tikkun. Possess +1 years of experience In an Information Technology Sector. Skilled in resolve issues related to computers, network, software, data analyst and skilled in Penetration testing.

# Curriculum Vitae

### Skills & abilities

The ability to clearly communicate findings, risks, and recommendations to non-technical stakeholders, The ability to think like an attacker and creatively solve problems, I work good with data, The ability to preprocess and clean data to ensure it is suitable for analysis and I can offer step-by-step troubleshooting advice for a wide range of software and hardware issues and Trading

# Communication

I believe one of my strong suits in communication is my ability to listen carefully and understand different perspectives and I adapt my communication style based on the audience and context to ensure that my message is understood.

# Education

Richfield College Institution 2020–2021

Information Technology in Technical Support

Digital Youth Academy 2023–2023

CompTIA Pentest+ & Cisco Cybersecurity

Afrika Tikkun Services 2023–2023

Network Administration Network Security System Administration Project Management

# Experience

Naspers Limited/ Prosu 2023-2024

Data Quality Analyst (Intern) & QA Software Testing

Praxis 2023-2023

Penetration Testing

Shasha Technologies 2021-2022

Technical Support Technician

#### Reference

Can be provided upon Request.